(Jun Hee, Ko You)
(جون هي ، كو يو)
(SEHUN)
(SEHUN)
(Jo Joon Young)
(جو جون يونغ)
(Jang Yeo Bin)
(جانغ يو بين)
(All That We Loved)
(كل ما أحببناه)
Han So Yeon.
هان سو يون.
I just saw the wrong thing, right?
لقد رأيت الشيء الخطأ للتو ، أليس كذلك؟
Can I look in your bag?
هل يمكنني النظر في حقيبتك؟
(Joon Young loves Jun Hee.)
(جون يونغ يحب جون هي.)
Hey.
يا.
Are you seriously...
هل أنت جاد...
- Actually, I... - You thief.
- في الواقع ، أنا ... - أنت لص.
(Joon Young loves Jun Hee.)
(جون يونغ يحب جون هي.)
Am I misreading the situation?
هل أخطأت في قراءة الموقف؟
No.
لا.
- Where did you... - Where did I steal it from?
- من أين لك .. - من أين سرقتها؟
I don't know where I stole it from.
لا أعرف من أين سرقته.
(Episode 6: Sadness Brings About a Strong Will)
(الحلقة 6: الحزن يولد إرادة قوية)
(Year 2023)
(عام 2023)
Hey, did you see So Yeon's article?
مرحبًا ، هل رأيت مقال So Yeon؟
Do you want a sandwich?
هل تريد شطيرة؟
Oh, this has peanut sauce in it.
أوه ، هذا به صلصة الفول السوداني.
Send me some papers on PMS-related kleptomania...
أرسل لي بعض الأوراق حول هوس السرقة المتعلق بـ PMS ...
or impulse control disorder if you have any.
أو اضطراب السيطرة على الانفعالات إذا كان لديك أي منها.
What?
ماذا؟
Okay.
تمام.
(Year 2006)
(سنة 2006)
Did Ko You come to school?
هل كو أتيت إلى المدرسة؟
I guess he skipped class with Han So Yeon.
أعتقد أنه تخطى الصف مع هان سو يون.
Hey, you're here. Where's Ko You?
مرحبًا ، أنت هنا.  أين كو أنت؟
I hear she transferred schools a lot.
سمعت أنها نقلت المدارس كثيرًا.
Then how did Han So Yeon buy it?
ثم كيف اشتراها Han So Yeon؟
(Joon Young loves Jun Hee.)
(جون يونغ يحب جون هي.)
You thief.
أنت لص.
Ko You. Did you lose a match?
كو أنت.  هل خسرت مباراة؟
Did you lose?
هل فقدت؟
No.
لا.
He must've fought with Han So Yeon.
لابد أنه قاتل مع هان سو يون.
Hi, Dunk.
مرحبًا دونك.
Gosh.
يا الهي.
Fine. You can have it.
بخير.  تستطيع الحصول عليه.
That's not the only photo I have of her.
هذه ليست الصورة الوحيدة التي أمتلكها لها.
Did you fight with So Yeon?
هل تشاجرت مع So Yeon؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Give this to Ms. Mo.
أعط هذا للسيدة مو.
Hey.
يا.
(Joon Young loves Jun Hee.)
(جون يونغ يحب جون هي.)
- Where did you find it? - I just found it.
- اين وجدتها؟  - لقد وجدتها للتو.
Just found it where?
فقط وجدت أين؟
I don't know. Just give it to Ms. Mo.
لا أعرف.  فقط أعطه للسيدة مو.
(Joon Young loves Jun Hee.)
(جون يونغ يحب جون هي.)
Hey.
يا.
Are you seriously...
هل أنت جاد...
- Gosh. I'm sorry. - Oh, dear.
- يا إلهي.  أنا آسف.  - يا عزيزي.
Gosh, she should be careful.
يا إلهي ، يجب أن تكون حذرة.
My goodness.
رباه.
- Why? - Do your friends tease you...
- لماذا؟  - هل يضايقك أصدقاؤك ...
for being left-handed?
لكونه أعسر؟
No.
لا.
I'm just trying to use both hands.
أنا فقط أحاول استخدام كلتا يديه.
It's good for your brain.
إنه جيد لعقلك.
- I see. - Oh, right.
- أرى.  - صحيح.
Wait.
انتظر.
Where did you find this?
أين تجد هذا؟
Ko You must've gone looking for it at the café you go to.
كو لابد أنك ذهبت للبحث عنه في المقهى الذي تذهب إليه.
Gosh, how did he find this?
يا إلهي ، كيف وجد هذا؟
You must've had a hard time.
لابد أنك مررت بوقت عصيب.
I couldn't find it anywhere, no matter how hard I tried.
لم أتمكن من العثور عليه في أي مكان ، مهما حاولت بصعوبة.
My goodness.
رباه.
Han So Yeon.
هان سو يون.
Do your friends tease you for being left-handed?
هل يضايقك أصدقاؤك لأنك أعسر؟
Ms. Mo?
السيدة مو؟
Stop it. I was just copying you.
توقف عن ذلك.  كنت فقط أقوم بنسخك.
It's super awkward. Don't do it!
إنه أمر محرج للغاية.  لا تفعل ذلك!
(Eyesight, fear of birds)
(البصر ، الخوف من الطيور)
Right hand, eyesight, fear of birds,
اليد اليمنى ، البصر ، الخوف من الطيور ،
basketball, Son Ye Jin, Ko You.
كرة السلة ، سون يي جين ، كو يو.
(Aller-check)
(فحص Aller)
I want banana-flavoured milk.
أريد حليب بنكهة الموز.
- Banana-flavoured milk? - No, strawberry-flavoured milk.
- حليب بنكهة الموز؟  - لا ، حليب بنكهة الفراولة.
- Hey, so what happened with her? - Come on.
- مهلا ، فماذا حدث معها؟  - تعال.
Hey. You guys stay here.
يا.  أنتم يا رفاق ابقوا هنا.
- What? - Hey, where are you going?
- ماذا؟  - مرحبا، إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
You remember me, don't you?
أنت تتذكرني ، أليس كذلك؟
I hear we transferred around the same time.
سمعت أننا انتقلنا في نفس الوقت تقريبًا.
Isn't that a coincidence?
أليست هذه مصادفة؟
Miss?
يفتقد؟
What's this?
ما هذا؟
Why? Is she yours?
لماذا؟  هل هي لك
Is he yours or not?
هل هو لك ام لا؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Hey, you...
يا هذا...
Answer me!
يجيبني!
Hey, Jeon Sang Kyu. Don't get into trouble again.
مرحبًا ، جون سانغ كيو.  لا تقع في المشاكل مرة أخرى.
Okay.
تمام.
Gosh, you make a cute couple.
يا إلهي ، أنت تصنع زوجين لطيفين.
Hey. Call me after you break up with him.
يا.  اتصل بي بعد الانفصال عنه.
(Regular checkups)
(فحوصات منتظمة)
Do you go around lying to people these days?
هل تتجول في الكذب على الناس هذه الأيام؟
I heard you've been saying that our son is the top student in class.
سمعت أنك كنت تقول أن ابننا هو أفضل طالب في الفصل.
Oh, that? I meant Jun Hee.
أوه ، هذا؟  قصدت جون هي.
Oh, Jun Hee.
أوه ، جون هيي.
Drink this.
اشرب هذا.
- Doesn't this belong to someone? - I guess it found its owner.
- ألا يخص هذا أحد؟  - أعتقد أنها وجدت صاحبها.
Rumours are spreading that we're going out. Did you know?
تنتشر الشائعات بأننا نخرج.  هل كنت تعلم؟
Who here doesn't know that we're married?
من هنا لا يعرف أننا متزوجون؟
Who talked such nonsense...
من تحدث مثل هذا الهراء ...
Was it Nurse Kim?
هل كانت الممرضة كيم؟
No.
لا.
It was me.
لقد كان أنا.
My gosh.
يا إلهي.
What's wrong with me? Why is my heart fluttering?
ما خطبتي؟  لماذا قلبي يرفرف؟
What is your secret?
ما هو السر الخاصة بك؟
You said I had to know others' secrets to understand them.
قلت إن علي معرفة أسرار الآخرين لفهمها.
I steal.
أنا أسرق.
That was my secret.
كان هذا سري.
Can you understand it?
هل تستطيع فهم ذلك؟
Why do you do it?
لماذا فعلت ذلك؟
If you can't understand it, just leave.
إذا لم تستطع فهمها ، فقط غادر.
Who'd understand it?
من سيفهمها؟
What, then? Do you want me to apologize?
ماذا بعد؟  هل تريد مني أن أعتذر؟
You steal things before your period.
أنت تسرق الأشياء قبل دورتك الشهرية.
It's an impulse control disorder...
إنه اضطراب السيطرة على الانفعالات ...
caused by premenstrual syndrome.
بسبب متلازمة ما قبل الحيض.
(Year 2023)
(عام 2023)
When I heard you became a psychiatrist,
عندما سمعت أنك أصبحت طبيبة نفسية
I was so happy.
كنت سعيدا جدا.
You were one of the people I wanted...
كنت من الأشخاص الذين أردتهم ...
to be understood by.
ليتم فهمه من قبل.
Perhaps...
ربما...
I thought you might...
أعتقد أنك قد...
already know about it.
تعرف بالفعل عن ذلك.
It's a psychiatric disorder,
إنه اضطراب نفسي ،
which can be cured.
الذي يمكن علاجه.
Have you sought treatment?
هل طلبت العلاج؟
Yes.
نعم.
It gets better when I'm undergoing treatment.
يتحسن الوضع عندما أخضع للعلاج.
Then like now,
ثم مثل الآن ،
it comes back.
يعود.
Right now,
الآن،
it's comforting to know...
من المريح معرفة ...
that there is at least one person who understands me.
أن هناك شخصًا واحدًا على الأقل يفهمني.
It's...
إنه...
comforting?
مطمئن؟
Yes.
نعم.
It is comforting...
إنه مطمئن ...
indeed.
بالفعل.
I can stay at your place for a little longer, right?
يمكنني البقاء في مكانك لفترة أطول ، أليس كذلك؟
I have nowhere to go.
انا لا امتلك مكان لاذهب اليه.
The reporters are everywhere.
المراسلون في كل مكان.
My place? Well, that's...
مكاني؟  حسن هذا...
Pick up some hair treatment after work tomorrow.
التقط بعض علاجات الشعر بعد العمل غدًا.
There's none in the bathroom.
لا يوجد شيء في الحمام.
What?
ماذا؟
Fine.
بخير.
(Yeonga)
(يونجا)
(Year 2006)
(سنة 2006)
Ms. Mo!
السيدة مو!
Hi.
أهلاً.
So Yeon!
لذا يون!
Yes.
نعم.
Can you close up instead of me today?
هل يمكنك أن تغلق بدلا مني اليوم؟
No, I have to hurry home.
لا ، لا بد لي من الإسراع إلى المنزل.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Grandma.
الجدة.
Yes?
نعم؟
Would you be happy if I were more like You?
هل ستكون سعيدًا لو كنت مثلك أكثر؟
You mean, Ko You?
تقصد كو أنت؟
Why are you asking such a question?
لماذا تسأل مثل هذا السؤال؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Do you think I favour You?
هل تعتقد أني أفضلك؟
No, it's not that.
لا ، ليس هذا.
I know you like us both equally, Ms. Mo.
أعلم أنك تحبنا على حد سواء ، السيدة مو.
You sounded like You just now.
لقد بدوت وكأنك الآن.
And that made you smile?
وهذا جعلك تبتسم؟
Grandma.
الجدة.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
- See you in a bit. - Okay.
- اراك قريبا.  - تمام.
- All right. - Get going.
- حسنًا.  - استمر.
(Convenience Store)
(محل بقالة)
Hello.
مرحبًا.
(New)
(جديد)
So Yeon.
لذا يون.
Excuse me!
اعذرني!
Mind your own business.
اهتم بشؤونك الخاصة.
You're not going to...
أنت لن ...
ask me anything?
اسألني اي شئ؟
Even if you asked me something, I wouldn't know what to say.
حتى لو سألتني شيئًا ، فلن أعرف ماذا أقول.
In this world, there are many things that can't be explained in words.
في هذا العالم ، هناك العديد من الأشياء التي لا يمكن تفسيرها بالكلمات.
Did You...
هل فعلت...
see it too?
أراه أيضًا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Jun Hee is not picking up.
جون هي لا تلتقط.
Where did he go?
إلى اين ذهب؟
Gosh.
يا الهي.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
You let Ms. Mo go home alone. Where have you been?
تركت السيدة مو تذهب إلى المنزل بمفردها.  أين كنت؟
Oh, I had to do something quickly...
أوه ، كان علي أن أفعل شيئًا بسرعة ...
What did you have to do?
ماذا عليك أن تفعل؟
You didn't even pick up.
أنت لم تلتقط حتى.
That's right.
صحيح.
I just went for a walk.
أنا فقط ذهبت في نزهة على الأقدام.
I'm hungry.
أنا جائع.
This guy keeps saying he's hungry.
هذا الرجل يقول باستمرار إنه جائع.
I have to stop by the bookstore.
عليّ أن أتوقف عند محل بيع الكتب.
Pick a place. I'll meet you there.
اختر مكانا.  سألاقيك هناك.
Sure. Be quick, okay?
بالتأكيد.  كن سريعا ، حسنا؟
What shall we eat? Shall we have toast again?
ما نأكل؟  يجب علينا نخب مرة أخرى؟
Toast, again? Come on.
نخب مرة أخرى؟  تعال.
Did You...
هل فعلت...
see it too?
أراه أيضًا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Hey.
يا.
Stop looking at me like that!
التوقف عن النظر في وجهي من هذا القبيل!
Is that all you can do?
هل هذا كل ما يمكنك فعله؟
- Come on. - You've got no money?
- تعال.  - ليس لديك مال؟
Smile a little, okay?
ابتسم قليلاً ، حسنًا؟
Think of us as your friends.
فكر فينا كأصدقائك.
Pluck up some courage.
استجمع بعض الشجاعة.
Have you lost your mind?
هل فقدت عقلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
I've lost my mind.
لقد فقدت عقلي.
(Americano, Refreshing Beverages)
(أمريكانو ، مشروبات منعشة)
I steal.
أنا أسرق.
That was my secret.
كان هذا سري.
Can you understand it?
هل تستطيع فهم ذلك؟
How could I understand that?
كيف أفهم ذلك؟
What? I can have one more?
ماذا؟  يمكنني الحصول على واحد آخر؟
- Sure, go for it. - You're so nice to me these days.
- بالتأكيد ، اذهب لذلك.  - أنت لطيف معي هذه الأيام.
Jun Hee said he'd be quick.
قال جون هي أنه سيكون سريعًا.
(Toast)
(خبز محمص)
He's not here yet.
إنه ليس هنا بعد.
You shouldn't have crossed the line.
لا يجب أن تكون قد تجاوزت الخط.
(Toast)
(خبز محمص)
What's taking him so long?
ما الذي ياخذه وقتا طويلا؟
Hey, watch. This is the last one.
مرحبًا ، شاهد.  هذا هو آخر واحد.
Hey, it hurts!
مهلا ، هذا مؤلم!
Hey!
يا!
Biting counts as cheating.
العض يعتبر غشًا.
Bring it on.
اجلبه.
Are you high or something?
هل انت منتشي او شيء من هذا القبيل؟
(All That We Loved)
(كل ما أحببناه)